## IRYNA NFPRANOVA

i.nepranova@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/iryna-nepranova

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

A responsible, enthusiastic, reliable person with great experience working in a bank. I'm interested in Front-End development and everything related to it. In a short time, I have developed a deep understanding of web-based processes. I consider myself a fast learner with a great passion for new knowledge and technology. I would like to become a valuable member of your team.

### **Key Skills, Software & Apps:**

JavaScript - HTML - CSS - SCCS - Bootstrap - React - Git - Figma

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of International Economics, East Ukrainian National University named after Volodymyr Dahl, Luhansk, Ukraine | 2013

#### **Continuing Education:**

Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate, Coursera | 2023

Front-End Pro, Computer School Hillel, Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2022

Front-End Basic, Computer School Hillel, Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2019

The Fundamentals of Software Testing, QA TestLab Training Center, online, Ukraine | 2018

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## EXPERT, JSC "OTP Bank", Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2018-2019

- Selling bank products: credit cards, loans, premium debit cards, insurance
- Consulting concerning the bank's products current or future clients
- Researching and verifying account information and resolving problems for customers as necessary
- Achievement of individual goals and contribution to overall branch goals achievement

PERSONAL FINANCIAL CONSULTANT, JSC "Ukrsibbank", Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2016-2018

- Selling bank products: credit cards, loans, premium debit cards, insurance
- Consulting concerning the bank's products current or future clients
- Researching and verifying account information and resolving problems for customers as necessary
- Achievement of individual goals and contribution to overall branch goals achievement

## SENIOR INSPECTOR, The state department of revenue services in Luhansk City, Luhansk, Ukraine | 2013-2015

- Advising clients on financial matters
- Preparing and filing tax documents
- Creating reports

### SOFT SKILLS

- Fast learner
- Adaptability
- Collaboration
- Result-oriented
- Time management

### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

Ukrainian: Native

Russian: Fluent

# My projects at Github:

https://iryna-nepranova.github.io/portfolio/

https://github.com/Iryna-Nepranova